A common statement that people make to me is, you know, if people don't think like you, then you think they're wrong.
Yes. Because I used to think like them and I was wrong.
Like, I used to think that the Democrats were an opposition party. I was wrong.
I used to think that it was enough to just, you know, protest, like showing a number of bodies out there.
I was wrong. I used to think that it was really positive that there was a black president.
I was wrong. And I was wrong within the framework that I grew into of humanism.
Of understanding that if there's a world that I want where there are resources for everyone, there is a root cause to that.
And that the things that I thought were right are actually very integral parts of the root cause.
So I was wrong. And once I grew and learned and understood more.
And became grounded in a very clear understanding of not only what I would love the world to be, but what it could be.
I had to admit that I was wrong.
And then commit to doing everything in my power to not let folks go on the same path that I was on as long as I was on it.
Also completely unrelated, I produced the two beats you're about to hear right now.
I have to admit that I was wrong.
And it was very clear because of the two beats you were almostone of the two beats you weren't leading now.
And I was just saying.
Oh yeah, that experience is kind of...
переп sentence as local as local is to get the search zone almostout.
That experience burst of practice now every year, you're going to focus on it again.